Guide to the Broadway Tabernacle Church and Society Papers 1835-1980 (Bulk 1840-1970) MS 74
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Papers
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Broadway Church Trust for Community Renewal, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Action Committee, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Education and Action Committee (1), 1966-1970 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Education and Action Committee (2), 1969-1971 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, refugee rescue issue, [1978-1979] (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons, "A Study of Space Needs as Related to Program", undated (Box 73)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons, "Training Kit for BUCC", undated (Box 73)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons, "Information Kit, BUCC", undated (Box 73)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons, "Preliminary Report of the Self-Study Committee of the Presbytery of New York City", 1968 (Box 73)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons (1), 1960-1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons (2), 1968-1976 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin Sermons, "An Introduction to BUCC", 1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, Lawrence Durgin papers, 1969-1979 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Tabernacle Society employee application cards, [1940-1969] (Box 74)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Tabernacle Society employee withholding exemption certificates (1), [1940-1969] (Box 74)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Tabernacle Society employee withholding exemption certificates (2), [1940-1969] (Box 74)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Congregational Church, payroll - Board of Trustee records, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Congregational Church, payroll sheets, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Congregational Church, payroll records, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Congregational Church, payroll sheets, 1960-1962 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Employee Records, Broadway Congregational Church, payroll sheets, 1960-1964 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Church School registration and student information, records books, 1960-1970 (Box 75)
  - Church School registration and student information, registration cards, 1946-1951 (Box 75)
  - Church School registration and student information, registration cards, 1950-1957 (Box 75)
  - Church School registration and student information, registration cards, 1961-1962 (Box 75)
  - Pastoral Advisory Committee, 1929 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Pastoral Selection Committee (1), 1947-1949 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Pastoral Selection Committee (2), 1947-1949 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Pastoral Selection Committee (3), 1947-1949 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Pastoral Selection Committee (4), 1949 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Pastoral Supply: Reverend Penner, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Pastoral Supply: expenses, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Pastoral Committee, Reverend Joseph D. Huntley, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee Materials and Ballots, voting membership, 1960 February 25 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee Materials and Ballots, pastoral selection, 1960 September 21 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee Materials and Ballots, membership eligibility cards, 1960 (Box 77)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee Materials and Ballots, pastoral selection ballots (1), 1960 (Box 77)
  - Pastoral Supply Committee Materials and Ballots, pastoral selection ballots (2), 1960 (Box 77)
- Series III: Real Estate
  This series contains eight boxes of real estate documents.
  - Real estate, Frank Fahy, 1933-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Real estate, Loyall A. Osborne, 1933-1950 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Real estate, Drs. R.C. and E.S. Funk, 1933-1952 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Real estate, Guiseppe Florio, 1929-1952 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Real estate, Dora Hazelkorn, 1932-1958 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Real estate, Beslou Holding Corporation #1, 1928-1942 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Real estate, Beslou Holding Corporation #2, 1943-1957 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Real estate, Adee Avenue Corporation, 1928-1955 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Real estate, W.B. Kirkpatrick, 1933-1951 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Real estate, Dorothy A. McEntee, 1929-1957 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Real estate, T.G. and E. Miner, 1933-1950 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Real estate, F.C. and E. Klune, 1932-1951 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Real estate, John Hoffman, 1931-1955 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Real estate, Alfred B. Stoddard, 1931-1955 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Real estate, Harold A. Calahan, 1933-1951 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Real estate, Jemina Herald, 1933-1955 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Real estate, Sidney Rosenfeld, 1933-1955 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Real estate, Benjamin Stebbins, 1941-1961 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Real estate, Kate Schweit, 1941-1956 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Real estate, Gordon Pollock, 1941-1956 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Real estate, Sevrin A. Haram, 1943-1963 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Real estate, B.L. Meyers, 1943-1955 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Real estate, New York Egg Auction, 1944-1955 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Real estate, Nettie S. Finkle, 1944-1957 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Real estate, Cedric Realty Company, Inc., 1943-1956 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Real estate, Jacob B. Schiedt, 1943-1950 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Real estate, Albert and Gertrude Doloff, 1945-1951 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Real estate, Louise Asher, 1945-1951 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Real estate, Jack-Martin Auto Sales, Inc., 1946-1962 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Real estate, Julius Jay Perlmutter Association, Inc., 1946-1950 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Real estate, Kate Schweit, 1947-1952 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Real estate, Henry Englander, 1948-1968 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Real estate, Arnaud and Susan d'Usseau, 1950-1965 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Real estate, Henry and Elizabeth Fowler, 1950-1964 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Real estate, Van Twistern, 1952-1959 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Real estate, William Gurian, 1958-1965 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Real estate, BroTab Real Estate Corporation Archives, 1932-1970 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Real estate, BroTab Real Estate Corporation Journal, 1932 November 4-1934 December 31 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Real estate, 1% Amortization, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Financial transactions: bonds and mortgages, 1928, 1933 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Real estate: appraisal, 1935 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Real estate: Equitable Mortgage and Guarantee Company, 1930 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Real estate: Bernheimer Company, 1935 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Real estate: W.T.T. Company certificates, 1930-1941 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Real estate: Lawyers Mortgage Company meeting 100107, 1942 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Estates: Lizzie Morehouse, 1929-1933 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Estates: Anna R. Munro, 1906-1930 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Real estate: rentals, 1902-1904 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Unsorted documents regarding real estate transactions of Broadway Tabernacle Society, [1920-1949] (Box 83)
  - Unsorted documents regarding real estate transactions of Broadway Tabernacle Society, 1900-1968 (Box 84)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, real estate corporation, minutes of meetings, 1932 November 11-1941 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, real estate corporation, minutes of meetings, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, real estate corporation, bank stubs, 1944-1967 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, Consolidated Appraisal Company, 1938-1948 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society, building survey, 1948 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Broadway Congregational Church, Charles F. Rittenhouse audit materials, 1959-1967 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Congregational Church, inventory tool list, 1959 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Broadway Congregational Church, Pendleton and Pendleton, Incorporated, insurance, 1951-1958 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, 56th Street property, 1969-1972 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Broadway United Church of Christ, "The Multiple Dwelling Law", 1937 (Box 85)
- Series IV: Committees and Programs of the Church
  This series contains five boxes.
  - Society for Women's Work, bank stubs, 1961-1968 (Box 86)
  - Society for Women's Work, bank stubs, 1968-1979 (Box 86)
  - Men's League, 1889-1915 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Laymen's Fellowship, Men's Work, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Bible class, 1910-1917 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Missions Department Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Women's Club, [1904]-1938 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Women's Club minutes and reports, 1955-1956 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Women's Club minutes and reports, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Women's Club minutes and reports, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Women's Club minutes and reports, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Women's Club minutes and reports, 1960-1961 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Women's Club Treasurer's report, 1963, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Women's Club, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Society for Women's Work, 1901-1902 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Society for Women's Work, Recording Secretary's book, 1942 February-1952 January (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Society for Women's Work, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Women's Fellowship Lecture: W.F. Dingley, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Women's Fellowship of the Metropolitan Association, 1966-1968 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Women's Fellowship Constitution and By-Laws, revised, 1948, 1963, 1966, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Women's Fellowship minutes and reports, 1951-1968 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Women's Fellowship minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Women's Fellowship annual report, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Women's Fellowship documents, 1964-1971 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Women's Fellowship minutes and reports, 1968-1973 (Box 87)
  - Women's Fellowship, 1968-1973 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Women's Fellowship scrapbook, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Women's Fellowship certificate, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Women's Fellowship financial papers, 1972-1979 (Box 87)
  - Women's Fellowship receipts and bank statements, 1963-1980 (Box 87)
  - Camp Jefferson, log book volume 1, 1923 December-1934 August (Box 88)
  - Camp Jefferson, log book volume 2, 1934 June-1939 August (Box 88)
  - Camp Jefferson, log book volume 4, 1944 January-1948 July (Box 88)
  - Camp Jefferson, log book volume 5, 1948 July-1951 January (Box 88)
  - Camp Jefferson, log book, 1976 September-1978 November (Box 88)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., visitors' lists, reservation sheets, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Camp Jefferson, Constitution of the Outing Council and miscellaneous papers, 1938-1973 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Camp Jefferson, Palisades Interstate Park Commission contracts, 1941-1954 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., certificate of incorporation and minutes and by-laws, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., miscellaneous papers and forms, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., charter service orders, 1975-1979 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., financial records, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., general ledger, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., termination of fund and volunteer award, 1980, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Camp Jefferson, Prisoners' Family Transportation and Assistance Fund, Inc., bank statements and check stubs, Chase Manhattan Bank, 1972-1979 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Tower League: "The Broadway Spectator", 1938 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Tower League: Secretary's Notebook, minutes of meetings, 1946-1949 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Tower League: Secretary's Notebook, minutes of meetings, 1949-1951 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Tower League: Constitution, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Tower League: minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Tower League: minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Tower League: minutes, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Tower League: minutes, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Tower League: minutes, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Tower League: annual reports, 1951-1958 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Series V: Bethany Congregational Church
  This series contains three boxes.
  - Records of the Advisory Committee, 1877-1903 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Records of the Advisory Committee, 1904-1924 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of the Bethany Board, 1919-1928 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Journal - Bethany Church Records, [1872-1908] (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Journal - Bethany Church Records, 1907-1928 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Center Street Mission Annual Report, 1864 March 1 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - BroTab report regarding the establishment of missionary outreach in New York, 1865 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Bethany Mission: annual report, industrial school, 1861 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Bethany Mission: mission reports, 1870-1873 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Bethany Society: document to BroTab, 1874 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Bethany Mission: mission report, 1874-1875 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Bethany Church: reports, 1877-1879 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Bethany Society: records, 1873-1874 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Bethany Mission: proposed organization of Bethany Church, 1877 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Bethany Congregational Church: articles of organization, [1877], undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Bethany Mission: documents, 1882, 1883 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Bethany Congregational Church: documents, contracts, reports, letters, 1898-1903 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - BroTab buildings: Bethany Church, 1898-1903 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Bethany Congregational Church documents, 1901-1902 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Bethany Congregational Church: correspondence of Bethany Board, 1928 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Bethany Congregational Church: documents, sale of property proposal, 1912-1946 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, "Yearbook of the Bethany Church", 1888 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, collections and documents, 1902-1929 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, church rolls, [1929] (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, fiftieth anniversay, 1927 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, scrapbook, fiftieth anniversay, 1877-1927 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, history celebration with BroTab, 1940 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, Baptismal records, 1911-1928 (Box 93)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, Baptismal records, 1912-1919 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, memberships, marriages, 1900-1926; 1922-1930 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Bethany Congregational Church, BroTab pledge records, [1958] (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Series VI: Martha Memorial Reformed Church
  This series contains four boxes.
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, "...to the Committee of Broadway Tabernacle Church", 1878 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, documents, 1887 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, Constitution, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, Confirmation and Church Record Book, 1893-1910 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, maintenance, 1918 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, Pastor's Register, [1920-1928] (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, records, 1933-1937 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, papers, 1935-1936 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, records, 1937-1942 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, Consistory records, 1943 January-1957 March (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, financial records and bank statements, 1959-1964 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, unification with Broadway United Church of Christ, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, sale of property, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, announcement of scholarship fund, [1978] (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, record of membership addresses, 1907 (Box 95)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, church list, 1916 (Box 95)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, "The Constitution of the Reformed Church in the United States", 1908 (Box 95)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, James E. Wagner, "So You're a Consistoryman!", 1949 (Box 95)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, insurance policies, 1942-1961 (Box 95)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, marriage records, 1880-1881 (Box 96)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, marriage records, 1881-1889 (Box 96)
  - Martha Memorial Reformed Church, German Bible, undated (Box 110)
- Series VII: Visual Materials
  - Broadway Tabernacle Society real estate snapshots, 1928-1958 (Box 97)
  - Glass plates and slides relating to Church buildings and personnel, undated (Box 98)
  - Unsorted photographs of buildings, undated (Box 99)
  - Photographs of ministers and church activities, undated (Box 100)
  - Photographic blocks, copper on wood, depict ministers, church buildings, church activities, undated (Box 105)
  - Seven reels of audiotape, eleven boxes of slides, one envelope of slides, five reels of motion picture, one envelope containing key, [1950-1973], undated (Box 106)
- Series VIII: Architectural Sketches
  This series contains two boxes.
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, Esquisse-A The Nave, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, Esquisse-B The Nave, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, Taylor Chapel-Scheme C, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, Taylor Chapel, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, 56th Street Entrance, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, 56th Street Entrance-A, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Architectural presentation schematic sketches for Broadway Tabernacle 56th Street Church, 56th Street Entrance-B, Adams and Woodbridge Architects, [1951] (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, S-7224, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, S-2502, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, large meeting room 5th floor, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, library, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, dining room on 5th floor, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, vestibule, S-2332, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, vestibule, S-1406, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, main church, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, S-2654, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, S-7015, S-2478, S-2638, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, recreation hall, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, Taylor Chapel, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, Jefferson Hall, Taylor Chapel, entrance hall, main church, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, meeting-committee room on 6th floor, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, lobby to library, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 56th Street Church, electric fixture sketch, main chandeliers, [1951] (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Series IX: Blueprints and Offprints
  - Blueprints (22) for Broadway Tabernacle Church, 1951 June 18 (Box 103)
  - Offprints, proposed alterations to 211 West 58th Street, 1964 December 4 (Box 104)
  - Offprints, proposed building at 1756 Broadway, 1969 May 23 (Box 104)
- Series X: Newspapers and Oversize Papers
  - Charles E. Jefferson, "The Knighthood Needed Now", undated (Box 107)
  - "Ship Little James. These names were written by William Ives Washburn, Clerk of the Society", undated (Box 107)
  - "Ship Fortune. Names written by Reverend George Andrew Gordon, Pastor's Assistant", undated (Box 107)
  - "Ship Anne. Names written by George L. Leonard, Clerk of Church", undated (Box 107)
  - Untitled document signed by Lawrence C. Durgin and parishioners, [1960-1969] (Box 107)
  - "The Mayflower. These names were written by the pastor of the Tabernacle, Charles E. Jefferson", [1960-1969] (Box 107)
  - The Pacific, 1903 April 23 (Box 107)
  - The Advance, 1903 April 30 (Box 107)
  - The Congregationalist and Christian World, 1903 May 2 (Box 107)
  - The Scientific American, 1857 December 26 (Box 107)
  - The Christian Intelligencer, 1857 December 24 (Box 107)
  - Advocate and Family Guardian, 1857 December 15 (Box 107)
  - The New York Times, 1857 December 25 (Box 107)
  - New York Commercial Advertiser, 1857 December 25 (Box 107)
  - The New York Journal of Commerce, 1857 December 25 (Box 107)
  - Christian Advocate and Journal, 1857 December 24 (Box 107)
  - The Examiner, 1857 December 24 (Box 107)
  - Protestant Churchman, 1857 December 5 (Box 107)
  - The Evening Post, 1857 December 24 (Box 107)
  - New York Observer, 1857 December 24 (Box 107)
  - The Sun, 1857 December 25 (Box 107)
  - The Independent, 1857 December 17 (Box 107)
  - New York Tribune, 1855 December 25 (Box 107)
  - Newspaper scrapbook, 1914-1917 (Box 108)
  - Newspaper scrapbook, 1917-1921 (Box 108)
  - Newspaper clippings, [1900-1969] (Box 109)